<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Torres' Tech Blog</title><link>http://403unauthorized.github.io/</link><description>记录我的学习之路</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>leiyongqi1026@gmail.com (Torres)</managingEditor><webMaster>leiyongqi1026@gmail.com (Torres)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 09:16:26 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://403unauthorized.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Athena and Macie</title><link>http://403unauthorized.github.io/2021/10/athena-and-macie/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 09:16:26 +0900</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://403unauthorized.github.io/2021/10/athena-and-macie/</guid><description>Athena What is Athena Athena is a interactive query service which enables you to analyse and query data located in S3 using standard SQL.
Serverless, nothing to provision, pay per query / per TB scanned No need to set up complex Extract/Transform/Load(ETL) process Works directly with data stored in S3 Athena Use Case What can Athena be used for? Query log files stored in S3: e.g. ELB logs, S3 access logs etc Generate business reports on data stored in S3 Analyse AWS cost nad usage reports Run queries on click-stream data Macie What is PII(Personally Identifiable Information)?</description></item><item><title>Kubenetes on Centos</title><link>http://403unauthorized.github.io/2021/10/kubenetes-on-centos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 15:21:26 +0900</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://403unauthorized.github.io/2021/10/kubenetes-on-centos/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="/images/posts/kubernetes-on-centos/kubernetes-on-centos.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>Prerequisite A compatible Linux host. The Kubernetes project provides generic instructions for Linux distributions based on Debian and Red Hat, and those distributions without a package manager. 2 GB or more of RAM per machine (any less will leave little room for your apps). 2 CPUs or more. Full network connectivity between all machines in the cluster (public or private network is fine). Unique hostname, MAC address, and product_uuid for</description></item><item><title>Golang Fundamentals</title><link>http://403unauthorized.github.io/2021/10/golang-fundamentals/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 10:49:20 +0900</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://403unauthorized.github.io/2021/10/golang-fundamentals/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="/images/posts/golang-fundamentals/golang-fundamentals.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>Hello Golang Golang is developed and published by Google, Kubernetes - which is know as a tool for container orchestration, is mainly developed by Go, so Go is very important in Cloud Native. In this article, we are gonna introduce all kinds of grammars and data structure in Golang, also we will share some tips for programming. Declaring and Assignment Declaring a variable in Go is similar to JavaScript, you</description></item></channel></rss>